jobmarket.com.hk 2007-12-11

# JobMarket 求職廣場

|  **** |    
---|---  

**** JobMarket Online, www.jobmarket.com.hk, is owned and operated by A Wholly owned subsidiary of Sing Tao News Corporation Limited, Job Market Publishing Limited and its parents, subsidiaries and/or its affiliates (hereafter collectively referred to as "the Company"). Your use of the services ("the Services") available through this Internet site is subject to the terms and conditions set out in this Privacy Policy Statement ("Privacy Policy!"). 

**About this Privacy Policy Statement**  
This Privacy Policy will give you information about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information including personal information that you may provide via this Internet site. Please read this entire Privacy Policy carefully before using or submitting any information including your personal information to this Internet site. 

**Your Consent**  
The Service commits to provide a high quality service of job searching for you. In order to facilitate the Service, it is necessary for you to provide us with your personal information. Whenever you attempt to submit personal information through this Internet site, you will be asked to choose whether to accept or not to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy by selecting the "I Accept" or "I do not Accept" button. By selecting the "I Accept" button, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When you visit this Internet site, we may collect various types of information from you. 

  1. Registration is necessary prior to the use of the Service. You may be required to submit your personal information including but not limited to your name, [a unique log-in ID and password], address, telephone number(s), gender, age, date of birth, occupation history and responsibilities, professional qualification, education level, and e-mail address. 
  2. Your personal information may also be collected when you communicate with us via e-mails. Some of the information that you submit may contain personal data including but not limited to your full name, gender, age, occupation, education level, address, e-mail address, phone number. 
  3. This Internet site uses various technologies, such as Internet Protocol addresses, cookies, Internet pages and navigational data collection to gather certain information about you without your actively providing the information. 

**Purposes of Personal Information Collection**

  1. Personal information submitted by you will be used for helping you to identify appropriate employment opportunities through the Service. 
  2. Personal information collected may also be used for direct marketing and promoting purposes or other internal use, to improve the content of this Internet site or other sites operated by the Company or strategic or joint venture partners, protection of the Company's legal rights, and/or for compliance with the laws of Hong Kong Special Administrative Region including governmental or regulatory requirements. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information to third parties**  
Your privacy is highly respected by us and generally speaking, your personal information will only be disclosed to the participants of the Service with your prior written consent. Your personal information may also be made to third parties under certain circumstances, for examples: 

  1. Information may be disclosed to personnel, agent(s), adviser(s), auditor(s), contractor(s) or service provider(s) who provide services or advice to us in connection with our operations;
  2. Where it is necessary to take legal actions(s) against you on grounds of, including but not limited to, enforcing the terms of this Privacy Policy or other civil claims, your personal information may be provided to pertinent third parties for identifying and taking action(s) against you; 
  3. Where we are required to make disclosure under any law applicable or pursuant to any court order, whether within or outside Hong Kong.

However, you acknowledge that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the personal data which is transmitted by you to third parties and we are not responsible for the manner in which such data is used by the third parties. 

**Access to and Correction of Personal Information**  
Under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance of Hong Kong, you are entitled to request access to your personal information collected by us and request the correction or deletion of your personal information from our database upon making a written request by sending email to [enquiry@jobmarket.com.hk](mailto:enquiry@jobmarket.com.hk) or you may edit or amend such personal information at any time in this internet site. 

**Security**   
We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information submitted by you and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We are however not responsible for any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of your personal information that have occurred in circumstances beyond our control. You are also reminded to take all steps to safeguard your own username and passwords from being made available to unauthorized parties. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
This Internet site contains hyperlinks or references to other web sites. Please note that we do not control these links or web sites not operated by the Company and that, in any case, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those links or web sites. The hyperlinks are provided to you as a convenience only.

**Other Terms**  
Your use of this Internet site is subject to the Terms and Conditions posted on this Internet site which are subject to changes from time to time.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Internet site, you may contact us by email to [jobmarket@jobmarket.com.hk](mailto:jobmarket@jobmarket.com.hk) or mail to 17/F., Sing Tao News Corporation Building, 3 Tung Wong Road, Shau Kei Wan, Hong Kong. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**   
This Privacy Policy is subject to changes and revisions from time to time. Please check periodically for updated version before you provide any personal information to this Internet site.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 07 July, 2006.
